[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 14]
[الحلقة 14]
Because of this.
بسبب هذا.
Look at this.
أنظر إلى هذا.
This is the wood splinter I found
هذه هي شظية الخشب التي وجدتها
on the back of her head during the second autopsy.
على مؤخرة رأسها أثناء التشريح الثاني.
It matches the splinter found at the crime scene.
إنها تتطابق مع الشظية التي وجدت في مسرح الجريمة.
Is it possible
هل هذا ممكن؟
that the killer pushed Mrs. Chen down
أن القاتل دفع السيدة تشين إلى الأسفل
in a confrontation,
في المواجهة،
causing her to lose consciousness, miscarry,
مما أدى إلى فقدانها للوعي والإجهاض،
and eventually die?
ويموت في نهاية المطاف؟
In other words,
بعبارة أخرى،
the killer mistakenly thought Mrs. Chen was already dead,
اعتقد القاتل خطأً أن السيدة تشين كانت ميتة بالفعل،
feared being held accountable for the crime,
يخشى أن تتم محاسبته على الجريمة،
and simply staged
ومنظم ببساطة
a fake scene of Mrs. Chen hanging herself.
مشهد مزيف للسيدة تشين وهي تشنق نفسها.
Since we've concluded it's a homicide,
وبما أننا توصلنا إلى استنتاج أنها جريمة قتل،
we need to track down the mastermind behind this.
نحن بحاجة إلى تعقب العقل المدبر وراء هذا.
Don't you think
ألا تعتقد؟
Mrs. Chen's clothing
ملابس السيدة تشين
was too flamboyant?
هل كان مبهرجًا للغاية؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Let's not even talk about wearing mourning clothes.
دعونا لا نتحدث حتى عن ارتداء ملابس الحداد.
Since Lord Chen had just passed away,
وبما أن اللورد تشين قد توفي للتو،
her clothes were way too ostentatious.
كانت ملابسها مبالغ فيها للغاية.
Maybe
ربما
Mrs. Chen didn't like Chen Zhao.
السيدة تشين لم تحب تشين تشاو.
Why?
لماذا؟
I have found out
لقد اكتشفت
that Chen Zhao injured his genitals in his early years,
أن تشين تشاو أصيب بأذى في أعضائه التناسلية في سنواته الأولى،
which left him infertile.
مما جعله عقيمًا.
So the child Mrs. Chen was carrying
لذا فإن الطفلة التي كانت السيدة تشين تحملها
was most likely not Chen Zhao's.
على الأرجح لم يكن تشين تشاو.
What?
ماذا؟
No wonder he had to rely on medicine
فلا عجب أنه اضطر إلى الاعتماد على الطب
to boost his performance in the bedroom.
لتعزيز أدائه في غرفة النوم.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
a maid from the Chen Mansion once said...
قالت خادمة من قصر تشين ذات مرة...
Before Madam got pregnant,
قبل أن تصبح السيدة حاملاً،
she was in good health all the time.
لقد كانت تتمتع بصحة جيدة طوال الوقت.
But after she became pregnant,
ولكن بعد أن أصبحت حاملاً،
her health took a turn for the worse.
تدهورت صحتها.
So that means
وهذا يعني
Chen Zhao actually knew
تشين تشاو عرف بالفعل
the child Mrs. Chen was carrying wasn't his own.
الطفل الذي كانت السيدة تشين تحمله لم يكن ابنه.
It seems that Mrs. Chen
يبدو أن السيدة تشين
often met her lover secretly at night.
كانت تلتقي بحبيبها سراً في الليل في كثير من الأحيان.
Chen Zhao was also quite strange.
وكان تشين تشاو غريبًا أيضًا.
The child wasn't even his,
الطفل لم يكن حتى ابنه
so why didn't he force Mrs. Chen
فلماذا لم يجبر السيدة تشين؟
to end the pregnancy
لإنهاء الحمل
and divorce her?
ويطلقها؟
At the very least,
على أقل تقدير،
he should have sought revenge against the child's real father, right?
كان ينبغي عليه أن يسعى للانتقام من الأب الحقيقي للطفل، أليس كذلك؟
Not necessarily.
ليس بالضرورة.
What if he wanted this child
ماذا لو أراد هذا الطفل؟
and thus hid the truth?
وهكذا أخفى الحقيقة؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Chen Zhao was narrow-minded.
كان تشين تشاو ضيق الأفق.
He was a two-faced scoundrel.
لقد كان رجلاً ذا وجهين.
He would do anything for his own benefit.
كان سيفعل أي شيء من أجل مصلحته الخاصة.
There was no way he would raise someone else's child.
لم يكن هناك طريقة ليربي طفل شخص آخر.
I mean
أعني
he was a petty man
لقد كان رجلاً تافهاً
and would only raise the child
وسوف يربي الطفل فقط
for his own benefit.
لمصلحته الخاصة.
So you're saying
لذلك أنت تقول
Mrs. Chen's lover
عشيق السيدة تشين
holds a higher official rank than Chen Zhao?
هل يحمل رتبة رسمية أعلى من تشين تشاو؟
It is possible.
من الممكن ذلك.
Then that means
ثم هذا يعني
the killer is likely a high-ranking official.
من المرجح أن القاتل هو مسؤول رفيع المستوى.
The two must have gotten into some kind of dispute,
لا بد أن الاثنين قد دخلا في نوع من الخلاف،
and he killed Mrs. Chen by accident.
وقتل السيدة تشين بالخطأ.
How did you find out about Mrs. Chen's death?
كيف عرفت بوفاة السيدة تشين؟
The ghost-masked man led me there.
لقد قادني الرجل ذو القناع الشبح إلى هناك.
The ghost-masked man again?
الرجل المقنع الشبح مرة أخرى؟
Why is he everywhere?
لماذا هو في كل مكان؟
What on earth does he want?
ماذا يريد على الأرض؟
He probably intended to use me
ربما كان ينوي استخدامي
to take down the one who killed Mrs. Chen.
للقبض على قاتل السيدة تشين.
This ghost-masked man
هذا الرجل المقنع الشبح
likes using others to kill so much.
يحب استخدام الآخرين للقتل كثيرًا.
Is he doing justice for heaven?
هل هو يحقق العدالة في السماء؟
I just have a feeling
لدي شعور فقط
that this isn't as simple as it seems.
أن الأمر ليس بهذه البساطة كما يبدو.
Zhao.
تشاو.
Yes.
نعم.
Mao.
هذا كل شيء.
You two go ask around
اذهبا واسألا حولكما
and find out which officials
ومعرفة أي المسؤولين
were on good terms
كانوا على علاقة جيدة
with Chen Zhao and his wife.
مع تشين تشاو وزوجته.
-Yes.
-نعم.
Why did you kill Mrs. Chen?
لماذا قتلت السيدة تشين؟
Let's not even talk about losing our cash cow.
دعونا لا نتحدث حتى عن خسارة بقرتنا النقدية.
Aren't you afraid Lu Zhan will trace it back to us?
ألا تخاف أن لو تشان سوف يتتبع الأمر إلينا؟
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار.
She was threatening me with the account book.
لقد هددتني بدفتر الحسابات.
I lost my grip for a moment
لقد فقدت قبضتي للحظة
and killed her by mistake.
وقتلها بالخطأ.
But don't worry, My Lord.
ولكن لا تقلق يا سيدي.
I was careful.
لقد كنت حذرا.
Lu Zhan and the others will never trace it to us.
لن يتمكن لو تشان والآخرون من تعقبه إلينا أبدًا.
It had better be so.
من الأفضل أن يكون الأمر كذلك.
Have you found Mrs. Chen's
هل وجدت السيدة تشين؟
account book?
دفتر الحسابات؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
But
لكن
it seems Lu Zhan and the others
يبدو أن لو تشان والآخرين
haven't found out about the account book yet.
لم يتم معرفة دفتر الحسابات بعد.
We must not let Lu Zhan find that account book.
لا يجب أن نسمح لـ لو تشان بالعثور على كتاب الحسابات هذا.
Lu Zhan already knows about the Moon Stone.
لو تشان يعرف بالفعل عن حجر القمر.
If the account book falls into his hands,
إذا وقع دفتر الحسابات في يديه،
neither of us will be able
لن يتمكن أي منا
to keep our official positions.
للحفاظ على مناصبنا الرسمية.
Yes.
نعم.
I'll handle it right away.
سأتعامل مع الأمر على الفور.
Black Hawk.
الصقر الأسود.
At your service.
في خدمتكم.
Keep a close eye on him.
ابقي عينك عليه عن كثب.
If he's exposed,
إذا كان مكشوفا،
kill him.
اقتله.
[Northern Inspection Division]
[قسم التفتيش الشمالي]
Commander Li.
القائد لي.
It seems that your martial arts are impressive.
يبدو أن فنونك القتالية مثيرة للإعجاب.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Then your lightness skill must be good too, right?
إذن يجب أن تكون مهارة الخفة لديك جيدة أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
How about you teach me that?
ماذا عن أن تعلميني ذلك؟
This might not be appropriate.
ربما لا يكون هذا مناسبا.
I won't let you teach me for nothing.
لن أسمح لك بتعليمك مجانًا.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I'll give you at least one tael of silver per month.
سأعطيك على الأقل تيلًا واحدًا من الفضة شهريًا.
Two taels. That's my final offer.
تيلتان. هذا عرضي الأخير.
Deal.
اتفاق.
Lift your legs higher!
ارفع ساقيك إلى أعلى!
Lift your legs higher.
ارفع ساقيك إلى أعلى.
Higher!
أعلى!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1، 2، 3، 4، 5، 6، 7، 8.
Commander Li, you really are ruthless.
القائد لي، أنت حقا لا ترحم.
Only under a strict master can a disciple excel.
لا يمكن للتلميذ أن يتفوق إلا تحت إشراف معلم صارم .
This is just the beginning.
هذه مجرد البداية.
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
Higher.
أعلى.
My Lord.
سيدي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm practicing my lightness skill.
أنا أمارس مهارة الخفة الخاصة بي.
What's the point of practicing that?
ما الهدف من ممارسة ذلك؟
It's tiring and difficult.
إنه أمر متعب وصعب.
Wherever you want to go,
أينما تريد أن تذهب،
I'll just take you.
سوف آخذك فقط.
That won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
I prefer to rely on myself.
أفضّل الاعتماد على نفسي.
I don't like troubling others.
أنا لا أحب إزعاج الآخرين.
Don't disturb me.
لا تزعجني.
Hold steady!
ثبات!
So slow!
بطيئا جدا!
Good.
جيد.
This one is good.
هذا جيد.
Good. Hold still.
حسنًا، توقف.
Yu wants to learn the lightness skill.
يو يريد أن يتعلم مهارة الخفة.
Why doesn't she ask you or me?
لماذا لا تسألك ولا تسألني؟
She can ask whoever she likes.
يمكنها أن تسأل من تريد.
I don't have any right to interfere.
ليس لدي الحق في التدخل.
Since when have you been so generous?
منذ متى كنت كريماً هكذا؟
I've always been this way.
لقد كنت دائما بهذه الطريقة.
Well,
حسنًا،
why are you here instead of handling cases
لماذا أنت هنا بدلاً من التعامل مع القضايا؟
at the Ministry of Punishments?
في وزارة العقوبات؟
You're doing the same thing.
أنت تفعل نفس الشيء.
It's like the pot calling the kettle black.
إنه مثل القدر الذي ينادي الغلاية بالأسود.
Straighten your back! Straighten it!
افرد ظهرك! افرده!
Straighten it.
تقويمه.
Lift them up.
ارفعهم .
Hold steady.
ابقى ثابتا.
Don't move! Don't move!
لا تتحرك! لا تتحرك!
-Li Zhaoxia!
لي تشاوشيا!
Hold the position.
حافظ على وضعيتك.
Commander Li is truly annoying.
القائد لي مزعج حقًا.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
-Yu!
-يو!
Yu, are you alright?
يو هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Commander Li, your hands
القائد لي، يديك
are really beautiful.
جميلة حقا.
I'm even tempted to chop them off for my own collection.
حتى أنني أشعر بالرغبة في قطعها لمجموعتي الخاصة.
No, no, no.
لا، لا، لا.
I prefer collecting whole corpses.
أفضّل جمع الجثث كاملة.
My Lords, please stop joking.
يا أصدقائي، من فضلكم توقفوا عن المزاح.
Officer Huang,
الضابط هوانغ،
I just remembered I have things to do.
لقد تذكرت للتو أن لدي أشياء يجب أن أفعلها.
I can't teach you anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أعلمك بعد الآن.
I'll refund your money later.
سأعيد لك أموالك لاحقًا.
I'm leaving now.
سأغادر الآن.
Commander Li,
القائد لي،
you promised to teach me!
لقد وعدتني أن تعلميني!
Yu,
يو،
Commander Li is very busy.
القائد لي مشغول جدًا.
It's normal that he doesn't have time to teach you.
من الطبيعي ألا يكون لديه وقت لتعليمك.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
He's not the only one who knows the lightness skill.
إنه ليس الوحيد الذي يعرف مهارة الخفة.
You can just find another teacher.
يمكنك فقط العثور على معلم آخر.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Then I'll just find another teacher.
ثم سأبحث عن معلم آخر.
Lord Shen, do you
اللورد شين، هل أنت
have time to teach me?
هل لديك الوقت لتعليمي؟
He doesn't have time.
ليس لديه وقت.
I have time.
لدي وقت.
Since when do you have time?
منذ متى لديك الوقت؟
Then you can teach me, Lord Shen.
ثم يمكنك تعليمي، يا سيد شين.
It would be my honor to teach you, Yu.
سيكون شرفًا لي أن أعلمك، يو.
This way.
من هنا.
Straighten your arm.
قم بتقويم ذراعك.
Yes.
نعم.
Don't shake.
لا تهتز.
Okay, I won't.
حسنًا، لن أفعل ذلك.
It's all right. I'm here.
لا بأس، أنا هنا.
I'm letting go now.
سأترك الأمر الآن.
This leg.
هذه الساق.
Come on, straighten it.
هيا، قم بتقويمه.
Be careful.
احرص.
That's right!
هذا صحيح!
Shen Pan is such a sly bastard.
شين بان هو مثل هذا الوغد الماكر.
He clearly did that on purpose!
من الواضح أنه فعل ذلك عمدا!
My Lord, please calm down.
ربي اهدأ من فضلك.
Let's think this through.
دعونا نفكر في هذا الأمر.
Come on, hold steady.
هيا، اثبت.
I won't fall.
لن أسقط.
It seems
يبدو أنه
Yu is still angry with me.
لا يزال يو غاضبًا مني.
Zhao,
تشاو،
give me some ideas.
أعطني بعض الأفكار.
My Lord,
سيدي
why did you have to give her the cold shoulder
لماذا كان عليك أن تتجاهلها ؟
all night?
طوال الليل؟
You were so close to winning her over,
لقد كنت قريبًا جدًا من الفوز بها،
but you let Shen Pan steal your chance.
لكنك سمحت لشين بان بسرقة فرصتك.
Li Zhaoxia,
لي تشاوكسيا,
I asked you to give me advice,
طلبت منك أن تعطيني النصيحة،
not to pick at my faults here!
لا تنتقد أخطائي هنا!
Yes, yes. Let me think.
نعم، نعم. دعني أفكر.
Is this good?
هل هذا جيد؟
Well done, Yu.
أحسنت، يو.
What should you do?
ماذا يجب عليك أن تفعل؟
Have you thought of any good ideas?
هل فكرت في أي أفكار جيدة؟
I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
أنا أفكر. أنا أفكر.
What on earth should you do?
ماذا يجب عليك أن تفعل على الأرض؟
Like this.
مثله.
Yes.
نعم.
I've got it!
لقد حصلت عليه!
Good, hold steady.
حسنًا، اثبت.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
So many valuables.
الكثير من الأشياء الثمينة.
My Lord.
سيدي.
All these are...
كل هذه...
An apology.
اعتذار.
An apology?
اعتذار؟
Yu,
يو،
you're
انت
not still angry, are you?
لم تعد غاضبا، أليس كذلك؟
Angry? My Lord,
غاضب؟ يا سيدي،
I'm not that kind of petty
أنا لست من هذا النوع التافه
or narrow-minded person.
أو شخص ضيق الأفق.
My Lord,
سيدي
you know me so well.
أنت تعرفني جيدا.